Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Portraits (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a light moustache., 1969; ref149; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.4 x 4.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Children; Boys; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., 11 February 1972; ref150; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.6 x 3.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Syria; Boys; Children; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a light colored shirt., 1970; ref151; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Children; Boys; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a patterned blazer (linked ref 186)., Circa 1955-1975; ref152; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a suit jacket., Circa 1955-1975; ref153; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Boys; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man with a patterned blazer (linked ref 155)., Circa 1955-1975; ref154; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 6.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man with a patterned blazer (linked ref 154)., Circa 1955-1975; ref155; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., 29 February 1972; ref156; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 3.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 23 April 1971; ref157; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.1 cm (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a patterned sweater (linked ref 185)., February 1971; ref158; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.3 x 5.8 cm (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref159; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 3.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref160; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.1 cm (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A studio portrait of a boy (linked ref 148)., Circa 1955-1975; ref172; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 3.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a plaid shirt., 17 July 1971; ref173; Hadad, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Children; Boys; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref174; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 4.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Children; Boys; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 2 August 1972; ref175; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 3.8 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref176; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 3.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a button-up shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref177; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 x3.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref178; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 x 3.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref179; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 x 3 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1958; ref180; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 15 December 1969; ref181; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 x 3.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref182; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 x 3.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a sweater., 17 April 1972; ref183; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.1 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref184; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 x 3.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a patterned sweater (linked ref 158)., February 1971; ref185; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Children; Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy with a patterned blazer (linked ref 152)., 7 February 1970; ref186; Studio Al Assime, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Boys; Arabic Writing; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref307; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1955-1975; ref308; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref309; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a turtleneck., 27 February 1971; ref310; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a man wearing a blazer and a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref311; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Facial Hair; Signatures
  - A portrait of a man wearing tinted glasses., 16 October 1971; ref312; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a scarf., Circa 1955-1975; ref313; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Men; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Syria; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref314; 1 Photographic Prints; 3.5 x 2.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man., October 1971; ref315; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref316; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Men; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a patterned shirt., 25 April 1972; ref317; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Facial Hair; Men; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man., 16 June 1955; ref318; Studio Mesmar, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 3.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a girl weraing a head scarf., 19 August 1963; ref319; Studio Echbelia, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Girls; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Head Covers/Veils; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a girl with braided hair., Circa 1955-1975; ref320; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Girls; Children; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a necklace., Circa 1955-1975; ref321; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Women; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A negative print of a portrait of a woman (linked ref 323)., Circa 1955-1975; ref322; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Women; Jewelry; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Negative Prints
  - A studio portrait of a woman with a polka-dot blouse (linked ref 322)., Circa 1955-1975; ref323; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 3.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Jewelry; Women; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a woman wearing a floral brooch., Circa 1955-1975; ref324; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Women; Jewelry; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a woman., Circa 1955-1975; ref325; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Women; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man with mustache., 17 July 1972; ref326; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Facial Hair; Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a man wearing a jacket., 1966; ref327; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man smiling (linked ref 329)., 1966; ref328; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.8 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man (linked ref 328)., 1966; ref329; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.6 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A negative print of a portrait of a boy wearing a plaid shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref330; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 x 3.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Negative Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Signatures
  - A negative print of a portrait of a man with a mustache., Circa 1955-1975; ref331; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 3.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Negative Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Signatures
  - A negative print of a portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref332; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 3.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Photographic Prints; Negative Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Signatures
  - A negative print of a portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref333; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 x 3.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A negative print of a portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref334; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 x 3.7 cm (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache and patterned shirt (linked ref 336)., 12 April 1972; ref335; Studio Zenobia, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache and patterned shirt (linked ref 335)., 12 April 1972; ref336; Studio Zenobia, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.6 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Syria; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a boy with buttons on his collar., 9 March 1972; ref337; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref338; Studio Karwan (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria; Children; Boys; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a tie (linked ref 340)., Circa 1955-1975; ref339; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a tie (linked ref 341)., 22 February 1972; ref340; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 3.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a tie (linked ref 340)., 13 May 1971; ref341; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1 July 1971; ref342; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 5.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 12 February 1972; ref343; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man., 1 July 1971; ref344; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 12 April 1972; ref345; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 27 April 1972; ref346; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 4.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref347; Studio Najah (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref348; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 27 July 1971; ref349; Studio Rateb, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref350; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a striped shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref351; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref352; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Studio Photography; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man (linked ref354)., Circa 1955-1975; ref353; 1 Photographic Prints; 3.9 x 2.8 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A studio portrait of a young man with a light mustache (linked ref353)., Circa 1955-1975; ref354; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 x 3 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Signatures; Men
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 15 March 1971; ref355; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man., 27 February 1972; ref356; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1965; ref357; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., 28 February 1966; ref358; C. Almas [?], Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Damascus, Syria; Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref359; Abdel Nour, Damascus, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Men; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref360; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 x 3.2 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Syria; Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a checkered shirt., Circa 1955-1975; ref361; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 x 3 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Signatures
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref362; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 19 August 1964; ref363; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 4.5 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 2 March 1971; ref364; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 x 4.1 cm (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., 1969; ref365; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 3.9 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Calligraphy; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., Circa 1955-1975; ref366; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref367; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.6 x 6.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a leather jacket., 1970; ref368; Cairo Studio, Ahmed Hariri, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a baby being held up by an adult., 1968; ref369; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Children; Arabic Writing; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a plaid shirt., 15 May 1969; ref370; Studio Egypt, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref371; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a leather jacket., 17 February 1972; ref372; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 x 4.9 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref373; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.1 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Boys; Children; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy that has been drawn on., 24 April 1967; ref374; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 4.3 cm (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a tweed jacket., Circa 1955-1975; ref375; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.5 x 4 cm (Box 3, Folder 11)